(Penny:)But we were never, like, going out.
(Leonard:)Okay. Not to be pedantic,
the last I checked...
..."went out" was the past tense
of "going out"...
(Leonard:)...which I think we all know
is a popular euphemism...
(Leonard:)...for saw each other naked.
(Sheldon:)I'll just roll for you.
(Penny:)You have a problem
with Justin staying with me?
(Leonard:)What was your first clue?
Uh-oh. Industrial accident.
(Penny:)Know what?
Don't talk to me like an idiot.
I'm not talking to you like an idiot.
I'm saying the whole idea is idiotic.
"You accidentally stare at a helium-argon
laser. Lose one turn and a retina."
How's that not talking to me
like I'm an idiot?
(Penny:)It's my friend, it's my couch
and it's my freaking life.
(Sheldon:)It's also your roll.
(Leonard:)You know what? It is your life.
If you wanna have some stupid guitarist
stay on your couch, fine!
Why don't you just rent bunk beds
and invite the Black Eyed Peas?
Hey, if I wanna invite the line-up
of Lollapalooza to my apartment, I will.
(Penny:)It's none of your business.
(Leonard:)Do you know how childish you sound
right now?
-Oh, now I'm a child. Not an idiot anymore.
-Hey, the two aren't mutually exclusive.